Hello, my friends.
And welcome to exercise number 62.
We are asked to write a function that deletes it, given no that specific possession.
We have learned before and how to delete A. with a given note.
So we get the note that we are going to delete and we search it inside the search for it, inside the
linked list and we delete.
Now we need to create at this exercise a method called void called delete.
Note.
At position.
OK.
And we best as end invariable end.
So this and will indicate the index, the position of the link, at least that was then known inside
the link, at least that we are going to delete.
So was the video and think about how we should delete the note at a specific position.
By the way, I am waiting your solution in the comments below, and all the source codes of this exercise
are available to download from the Resources folder in our Udemy course.
OK, so let's begin developers first step check for the liability, OK?
If had equal equal to now or men and less than or equal to zero, then a return.
OK, now the second step create A..
No guarantee equal to had and create entirely as a value how to traverse up, then up to the node at
the given position.
Traversing mean we did to use the loop.
So three.
Finding the requested or that given?
No, OK, we need to search for it first in order to delete it.
Now for.
I equal to zero.
I can create I can create that here.
And I am equal to one because we have checked if this does not equal to none.
Current does not equal to none.
And I and I less than an hour and a plus a plus.
This were resolved.
What we are going to do current equal to the talk next game, we are jumping.
So from one to the last of the no until we reach current does not equal two, not equal to null.
We stop or.
Sorry, and I less than and so we specify and as the position that we are going to search for if we
found it, then foot care and equal care in the next.
Now we have found that
the note then if an is greater than the number of notes in the linked list, then return check for availability.
OK.
How to do that if Grant equal equal to none and then a return of gay.
Now we have created a method before it called delete don't in the exercise number six through one.
And we checked for it in the liability we have.
Check if a given note is had and then we have deleted it by changing that sequence and changing that
links.
So we are going to make use of it.
So we need to call the method that delete node method
delete note.
Okay.
And what we are going to pass is a note, a perimeter of type note.
So what is the note that we have found?
We have stopped at Kirtland, so we loops through that note.
We search for NW.
We find and we specify that the current node here is equal to the end now near Adelaide.
OK.
We have found that the node at the given position and we specified this as occurred and we have created
a node.
It's called Curtin and we have moved it until we reach there.
And now we delete the node by specifying and by calling the method delete node that's run and see.
Let me delete.
This is our link at least 99 to three and four.
I need to remove that node like three that we check
before printing here, the alt or delete to note that position to.
It's run and see.
At position three, we have because we have started from one, nine, three, nine, two and four.
So three have been removed.
OK, so we have removed that.
Not at position.
No.